创业公司
前情回顾
怎么着  你想来个游行庆祝  全套吗
So, what, you want the parade, the whole nine, all that?
好好让他入土为安
Put 'em in the ground right.
我们准备实现这个计划
We're ready to make this a reality.
尼古拉斯·塔尔曼和罗纳德·达西
Nicholas Talman and Ronald Dacey
都不会获得侦币的任何所有权
claim no ownership to GenCoin.
我知道你是什么来头
I know what you are.
那你应该明白为什么你最好别回头
So then you understand why it'd be best to never look back.
你像利用你生活中其他人一样在利用我们
You're using us just like you use everybody in your life!
你永远无法脱身
It never leaves you.
只是生意而已
It's just business.
亚历克斯·贝尔  我需要情报
Alex Bell. I need information.
你凭什么觉得我能弄到
What makes you think I can get it?
可伊莎贝尔·莫拉莱斯可以
Isabelle Morales could.
-我要我的人  -不行
- I need my people. - I can't.
罗纳德·达西  尼克·塔尔曼
Ronald Dacey, Nick Talman,
他们是侦币的真正英雄
they're the real heroes of GenCoin.
我不能开门
I'm not supposed to open it.
亚历克斯
Alex!
非常感谢
Thank you. Yeah.
很高兴再次与您交谈
Super good to talk to you again.
你在新办公室吗
So you're at the new offices right now?
没错  我们在温伍德
Yup. Yeah, we're here in Wynwood.
仍在壮大团队  努力推动发布进程
Still ramping up the team, trying to move towards launch.
侦币将何时发布
And when is that gonna be?
你是打算尽快发布还是...
Have you set a hard, fast date or...?
我们仍在不同平台进行测试
Well, we're still testing the beta on different platforms,
确认适用网络  以及其他必要准备
we're finding our network, all the necessary bits and pieces.
我们不想操之过急
We don't want to rush it, obviously,
但是我们觉得
but there's also the feeling that
亚历克斯·贝尔
侦币联合创始人
侦币应该快要发布了
the world shouldn't have to wait any longer for GenCoin.
确实如此
Well, it certainly seems that way.
你能不能给我做个讲解
If you could, go ahead and explain this to me,
因为一说到这类东西
'cause I guess I'm a little, I don't know, thick,
怎么说呢  我就有点懵
when it comes to these sort of things.
亚历克斯·贝尔
侦币联合创始人
侦币到底是什么
What is it?
和贝宝一样吗
Is it like a PayPal?
你觉得有什么区别
What would you compare it to?
贝宝是电子支付交易系统
Well, PayPal is a digital payment system.
本身并不是货币
It's not its own currency.
侦币却是
GenCoin is.
比如你可以拿一美元买东西
It's like... okay, so, you could pay for something with a dollar
收件箱
或是用日元
or you could pay for something with yen.
也可以用侦币
Or you could pay for something with GenCoin.
无主题
未知发件人
它本身就是货币吗
So, it actually is its own currency?
没错
Yes.
请听
{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs32\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&HC1FEF5&\t(2734,2943,\blur4)\t(2943,3026,\blur0)\t(2943,3110,\blur8)}创业公司
第一季  第十集
你喜欢这个发型吗
Do you like it like that?
可以吗
Is it okay?
可以
Yeah, it's all right.
你不必弄这个发型
'Cause you don't have to have it like that.
我真无所谓
I really don't care.
没事  妹
It's cool, sis.
-我臭吗  -什么
- Do I stink? - What?
我臭吗
Do I stink?
把那个给我  我不停冒汗
Give me that. God, I can't stop sweating.
多芬止汗喷雾
谢了
Thanks.
伊兹
Izzy?
有人找你
Someone to see you.
伊莎贝尔
Isabelle.
你收到我发的东西了吗
Did you get the stuff I sent you?
收到了
Yeah. Yeah, yes, I did.
我们...
Let's...
能找个地方谈谈吗
There is somewhere we can talk?
好
Yeah.
你本可以受到同等合伙人条例保护
The thing is, you would have been protected as an equal partner,
可这家第三方公司  伊甸田
but this third party, eden Field...
也是亚历克斯·贝尔的你知道吗
were you aware that Alex Bell owns it?
他是伊甸田的控股董事会成员
And he is a controlling board member of Eden Field,
从法律上来讲
which legally makes him
他有侦币三分之二的参与权
two-thirds participant in GenCoin.
不  这太扯了
No. No. That's bullshit.
他没跟我说过这事
He didn't tell me that part.
伊甸田与侦币签署的合同中都提到了
It's fully disclosed in Eden Field's contract with GenCoin.
合同  他根本没给我看过
"Contract"? He didn't show me that!
他不用给你看
He didn't have to.
他也知道你不会问他要
And he knew you wouldn't ask for it.
伊莎贝尔
Isabelle...
你怎么不早点来找我
why you didn't bring this to me?
我满心以为他就是那位伯乐
All I could think about was this was the dude.
这家伙有钱
This guy, he had the money,
他能让侦币变成现实
and he was gonna make it real.
我真的很遗憾
I'm really sorry about this.
把箱子放到引擎盖上
All right, go ahead and put it on the hood.
-吉勒斯  数数  -好
- Hey, Gilles, count that. - Okay.
亚历克斯不想来是吧
So I take it Alex didn't want to show, huh?
他比较忙  不过他让我转达问候
He's spread a little thin at the moment, but he sends his regards.
最好是这样
I'll bet you he do.
等等
Hey, hold up, though.
这里好像只有30万
This seem like only about 300 in here.
说好的是45万
You know it 'posed to be 450.
公司没批准我们提那么多钱
We were unable to get that amount approved.
你确定要搞成这样吗
Are you sure you want it to go down like this?
理解一下  罗  侦币
Try to understand, Ron. GenCoin...
我只知道你们钱没带够
No, I understand that you short.
这就是我的理解
That's what I understand.
你可以打给你的律师
You're welcome to call your lawyer.
不然就只好这样了
Otherwise, I'd let this one be.
真棒
Bravo!
不好意思
Permiso.
你在看守这些宝贝吗
Are you guarding the stash?
你是伊莎贝尔吧
Isabelita, huh?
你妈安排得真好
What a job your mom did.
肯定一大堆事要处理吧
Must have been a lot of chaos around here.
-是啊  -我了解马塔
- Yeah. - I know Marta. I know her.
她对这场婚礼很上心
Yeah, she...she took it very seriously.
是啊
Yeah.
最近怎么样
How have you been?
你从加利福尼亚来这里后
I feel like I didn't see you since you came from...
我就没见过你了
California, right?
一直在弄新东西
Just workin' on new stuff.
什么"新东西"  什么"新东西"
Como que "New stuff"? Como que "New stuff"?
亲爱的
Aye, mi amor.
你爸说你自己开了公司
Your dad told me that you start your own company!
什么科技公司  对吗
Something about tech, right?
他说你有间高档
Yes, yes, he told me you have a big,
宽敞的办公室  应有尽有
fancy office and everything.
我要把这瓶酒...
I'm gonna go take this...
拿给你男友吗
To your boyfriend?
一会见...
I will meet...
你又要偷藏老爸的啤酒
You stashing Papi's beer again?
不  我只是...
No, I just...
想自己待会儿
needed a minute.
我们马上要切蛋糕了
We're cutting the cake in a bit though, all right?
好
Yeah.
我马上过去
I'll be there.
戴尔
Delly?
怎么了
Yeah?
你真漂亮
You look beautiful.
我知道
I know.
你要记得锁侧门
You should try locking the side gate.
你怎么不走前门
What's wrong with the front door?
我觉得你不会开门
I didn't think you would open.
我...
I, uh...
有些话要说
I have some things I need to say.
我要解释一下
I need to explain myself.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
对不起
I'm sorry.
好吗
Okay? Um...
对不起
I'm sorry.
真好
Great.
道个歉没事了
Everything's better then.
听我解释
Let me explain myself.
我知道你要说什么
I think you know what you're gonna say.
我也被踢出来了  尼克
No, I got pushed out too, Nick.
我被洗出局了  我完了
I'm out of my own thing. I'm done.
他拉了一个第三方
He brought in a third partner.
是个服务器群组
This, uh, server farm.
一家网络管理公司
A network management company.
结果公司也是他的
It turns out that he owns it, too.
他就占了多数股份
Which makes him a majority,
然后直接投票把我踢出了公司
then he single-handedly voted me out.
律师说这叫恶意收购
The lawyers called it a hostile takeover.
是有这种东西
Yeah, it's a thing.
我的代码被他强占了
He owns my code.
侦币
GenCoin.
我毕生心血就这么归他了
My life's work, it's his just like that.
太惨了
Well, that sucks.
是啊  总之...
Yeah. Anyway...
总之你现在道歉
Yeah, anyway, now you're sorry,
是因为你一无所有
'cause you've got nothing.
我劝过他让你们回来
I tried to bring you guys back in.
我尽力了
I tried.
但你也知道  当时一团糟
But everything was a mess and you know that.
我束手无策
I didn't know what to do.
我只是想让侦币变成现实
I just wanted GenCoin to work.
我只在乎这件事
That's all I cared about.
这比你  我  罗尼都重要
It was bigger than you or me or Ronnie or...
好了  希望说完这些你能好受点
Okay, I hope that makes you feel better.
我送你出去
Let me show you the front door.
如果你之前
Maybe if you wouldn't
不把我当成疯子
have treated me like a fucking crazy person,
-尊重我一些  -你就是个疯子
- and had some respect for me. - You are a fucking crazy person!
你不了解我
You don't know me!
你知道你疯了
I know you're fucking crazy!
你什么都不明白  为什么呢
You don't know nothing. You know why?
因为你什么都不缺
You don't know because you have all of this.
你也不了解我  好吗
You don't know me either, all right?
-说话注意点  -有钱白人的通病
- So watch what you say. - Rich white people problems!
你不了解我  也不了解我的经历
You don't know me and you don't know what I've been through.
你也不知道我的经历
You have no idea what I've been through.
好可怜哦
Boo fucking hoo.
你老爸不要你了
Your daddy ran out on you.
-别这么说  -怎么了
- Don't fucking say that. Don't fucking say that. - What's wrong?
我们互相都不了解
I don't know you, you don't know me,
我不知道你脑子里...
and I don't know what goes inside your...
来啊  儿子
Come on, son.
就让你老爸这么虐你吗
You let your old man work you like that?
来啊
Come on.
来
振作点  再来
Come on. Hey, hey, try again. Try again.
背打我
Back me down.
好吧
A'ight.
防我吧
Try to stop me, a'ight?
来防我
Just try to stop me.
你怎么能让那贱人这么耍你
Why you let that bitch play you like that?
说什么呢  小子
The hell you talking, boy?
那个坐凯雷德过来的女人
The girl who come up in here in the Escalade,
带来一大笔钱
showed us a whole bunch of bills.
这事没那么简单
It's complicated.
我就说这么多
That's all I'll say.
你现在不是老大吗
Ain't you the man now?
这不是你的地盘吗
Ain't this your hood?
你就让那个白人婊子
And you gonna let some white bitch
在你的地盘上这样羞辱你吗
roll up in here and diss you like that?
那个白人婊子
That white bitch,
身边的俄国佬全副武装
she clipped up with the Russians.
我会拿到钱
Now, I'mma get that money.
但你得放聪明点
But you gotta be smart about that shit there.
爸  随便吧
Yeah, Pap. Whatever.
别跟我说"随便"
Don't "Whatever" me.
好吗
All right?
我们在谈正事
'Cause this some serious ass shit right here.
不带感情
Stone cold.
你要知道大丈夫...
You gotta know when to be the man...
能屈能伸
and when to be the bigger man.
明白吗
You feel me?
你就该把他们全杀了
Should have murked them all.
我就这意思
That's all I'm sayin'.
-是吗  -是
- Oh, is that right? - Yeah.
-把他们全干掉  -对
- I should have killed them all? - Yup.
-全部干掉  -对
- Just killed everybody there, huh? - Yup.
把他们全毙了  是吗
Just bap, bap, bap, bap? Just killed all them, huh?
-是  -直接干掉  是吗
- Yup. - Just shot 'em dead, huh?
-直接干掉  -一枪爆头
- Shot 'em dead. - Shoot 'em in the face!
-就这样干掉他们吗  -是
- Should've killed them like that, huh? - Yeah.
毙了他们  对吗
Killed 'em dead, right?
他们就不会再出现了
They ain't here no more.
全死翘翘了  就该杀了他们
They're gone. I should have just killed them, right?
给他们头上来一枪
You should have shot them in the face!
儿子  没事
Son, it's okay.
你做了该做的事
You did what you had to do.
明白吗
You understand this?
你做了该做的事
You did what you had to do.
明白吗
A'ight?
你没做错
You did right.
发泄一下吧
Just let that shit out.
不  不  没事的
No, no, no, no, it's all right.
好儿子
That's my boy right here.
This my boy right here.
没事了吧  我马上回来
You all right? I'll be right back, all right?
你做得很好  你做得很好
You did good. You did good.
她来这里干什么
The hell she doin' here?
-我们得谈谈  -听我们说
- We have to talk. - Just hear us out.
听着  我们都得谈谈
Listen, we all need to talk.
尼克  她来干什么  搞什么
Hey, Nick, what is she... come on, man.
-我知道  -太扯了
- I know. - It's ridiculous right here.
哪里扯
What's ridiculous?
你来这里就很扯  你心里清楚
You being here. You know what you did.
-尼克  把话讲清楚  -抱歉
- Come on now, Nick. You got some explaining to do. - I'm sorry.
不用他解释
He doesn't have to explain anything.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我为我的所作所为道歉
I am sorry for what I did,
我知道一句"抱歉"不能了事
and "Sorry" doesn't cut it,
我知道  但是除了抱歉
and I know that, but I have no other words
我不知道还能说什么
other than "I am sorry."
我们才是侦币的核心
This right here is GenCoin.
没有你们就没有侦币
There's no GenCoin without you.
我们有个夺回公司的计划
We had a plan to get the company back.
你想加入吗
You want in?
芬利
老天
Oh, Jesus Christ.
喂  你好
Hello. Hello.
明早见
I'll see you in the morning.
好
'Kay.
我把伊甸田的时间改到了十一点
I moved Eden Field to 11:00,
你可以多休息会儿
so you could get some rest.
我没事
I'm fine.
怎么了
What?
这是大势所趋
It had to happen.
我们给过她机会
We gave her fair chance.
有些狗拴不住
Some dogs can't be chained.
她会咬伤我们所有人
She would have bitten us all.
也许只是你
Maybe just you.
薇拉
Vera?
侦币不能落得跟其他项目一个下场
GenCoin can't wind up like the others.
不会的
It won't.
就是这位老兄偷了咱们的钱
So this the little nigga who took our cash.
这是亚历克斯所有空壳公司的产权史
Chain of title for all of Alex's shells.
还有02年起他赚的  花的
Plus, a paper trail for every single dollar
或者投资的书面记录
that he's made, spent, or invested since 2002.
她把他大学的色情网站账户都黑了
She even hacked all his porn accounts from college.
那就是图个开心
That was just for fun.
干得漂亮
Nice work.
你怎么拿到的
How'd you get it?
你来找我们前  我就把他给黑了
I hacked his shit way before you came to us.
这妹子不轻信别人
Our girl got trust issues.
那你们的条件呢
So... what's the catch?
条件...
The catch...
就是不能用这个勒索他
is that you're not gonna use that to blackmail him.
你...
You...
要替我们办事
work for us now.
你要用这些把他打垮
You're gonna use it to bring him down
而且不能让我们触犯法律
without implicating us in any legal activity.
你们还没弄清情况吧
I don't think you understand how this works.
-是吗  -是的
- We don't? - No.
罗尼  我们没弄清吗
Ronnie, do... do we not know how this works?
妹子  我也说不好啊
Shit, girl. I don't know. I don't know, man.
我们是...
Are we just...
这事他说了算吗  尼克
Does he got the drop on us, Nick?
难说
Oh, it's tough to say.
非常难
Super hard.
准备好就说一声
Let me know when you're ready. I'll press play.
这是什么
What is that?
戴耳机  听听看
Listen. Put it on.
为什么
Why?
你先听完再说
Why don't you listen and then we'll talk?
赶紧把录音听了
Just listen to the motherfucking tape.
这是你们的样带吗
This your demo?
请吧
Yeah, please.
-什么  -你把那姑娘杀了吗
- I'm sorry? - You kill the girl yet?
你说什么
What?
你把那姑娘杀了吗
You kill the girl yet?
你要是再敢问一遍
You ever ask me that again,
我就一枪毙了你
I'm gonna put a bullet through your head.
别再问我这个问题了
I don't want you asking me that again.
-她看到我了  -我知道
- She saw me. - Yeah, I know.
她看到了这个  也看到了你
She see this. She see you.
我知道  你是个天才
Yeah, yeah, I know. I know. You're a genius.
那烂摊子交给我  行吗
You let me deal with that, all right?
你帮我把钱拿到就好了
You deal with getting me my fucking money.
我们应该很快就要扩大团队规模
We're gonna probably need to scale up the team pretty soon.
至少还要两人
I want at least two new people
专门负责管理双端网络
who are solely dedicated to interfacing with Mimi
与米蜜进行对接
about network management on both ends.
我认识个本地工作的人  想见见吗
I have a guy who's based here if you want to meet him.
他经常去奥斯汀出差
He flies back and forth to Austin,
所以在伊甸田有些熟人
so he knows some of the Eden Field people already.
我想尽快跟他见面
I'd love to meet him as soon as possible.
你仍然想在二号发布吗
Are you still aiming to launch on the second?
最好吧
Ideally.
但测试版还没在全平台通过检测
But the beta hasn't been proven across all platforms yet,
-我还... -会成功的
- and I still... - It'll work.
我们会测试  会成功的
We'll test it, and it'll work.
二号发布没问题
So we can launch on the second.
尼科说可以在二号发布
Yes, well, Nico says we can launch on the second.
如果我们在二号发布
If we wanted to launch on the second,
我们能承受的日交易次数有多少
how many transactions per day do you think we'd be ready to host?
我们得加紧扩大规模
Well, we'd have to scale up way quicker.
这不是不可能
Um, it's not impossible.
只是要多花钱
Just takes money.
我们有钱
'Kay, well, we have money.
抱歉各位  稍等
Sorry, guys. Uh, one sec.
亚历克斯
Alex.
我认识你  我是菲尔·拉斯克
I know. Uh, Phil Rask.
联调局金融犯罪部
FBI, Financial Crimes.
-幸会  菲尔·拉斯克  -幸会
- Nice to meet you, Phil Rask. - You too.
回避一下
Uh, if you could...
抱歉叨扰  我知道你很忙
Excuse the interruption. I know you're busy.
没关系
Oh, uh, no, it's okay.
薇拉问过你要来点...
Can... uh, did Vera ask if you want...
问了  谢谢  我不喝
She did, thank you. Yeah, I'm fine.
好吧
Okay then.
你有何...
What, uh...
有何贵干
And how... how can I help?
我需要钱
I need money.
我知道明斯克的事
Yeah, I know about Minsk.
赫尔辛基的事
I know about Helsinki.
我...
I... I'm...
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
别跟我装傻
Don't fuck with me.
我有四百多页文件
I have over 400 pages of documents linking you
证明你与科斯塔·维托夫
directly to Kostya Vetrov
以及马克·叶戈罗夫有往来
and Mark Yegorov.
文件就在我这里
I have those.
不在金融犯罪执法网络
Not FinCEN.
也不在联调局或中情局
Not the FBI. Not the CIA.
就我一个人有
Me and me alone.
我不明白  你是在勒索...
I don't understand. Are you blackmail...
我就是在勒索你
I'm blackmailing you. Yeah.
你这房子里
Now, I'm going to assume
应该放了不少现金吧
that somewhere here you have a reserve of cash.
很好
Good.
把钱都装进包里
Well, I want all of it in there right now.
-我  -闭嘴
- I... - Shut up.
识相点  好吗
Be smart, okay?
那你就会放过我吗
And you'll leave me alone?
你得帮帮我
You have to help me.
求你了
Please.
帮帮我
Help me.
把文件销毁吧
Make them go away.
没问题
Pleasure.
[俄语]
谁给你的
Who gave you this?
这玩意是谁给你的
Who gave you this shit?
-好吧  -终于把院子收拾好了
- Okay. - The yard is finally back to normal.
-谢天谢地  -只花了两天
- Thank god. - It only took two days.
你航班什么时候  亲爱的
Hey, what time is your flight, nena?
-宝贝  -三点  三点
- Nena? - At 3:00. At 3:00.
但我马上得回去一趟
But I have to get back soon
埃迪应该还没开始收拾
'cause I'm sure Eddie still hasn't packed yet.
我好嫉妒
I'm so jealous. I mean,
我们很久没旅行了  她爸
we haven't gone away on a trip in forever, right, Papi?
-巴哈马呢  -天啊
- What about the Bahamas? - Oh, my God.
那是我们的蜜月
That was our honeymoon, okay?
-我知道  -我就这么点钱
- I know. - Hey, it's all I could afford.
意大利怎么样
How about Italy?
意大利
我还要多来点火腿
I'm gonna have some more of this ham right here.
是帕尔玛火腿
It's prosciutto.
珀出玛火腿  随便吧
Ponchuchokodou.
为什么不去意大利
Why don't we go to Italy?
好啊  不过你得乖一点
Okay, but you're gonna have to be very nice.
-天啊  -什么时候去
- Oh, my God. - When are we going?
-十三月  -很快
- Nevuary. - Soon.
好笑吗
You think that's funny?
欢迎来到小海地
你在想什么  她没在开玩笑
What do you think? She's not joking. What do you...
他们应该去古巴
You know what? They should have gone to Cuba.
她去古巴干什么
What is she gonna do in Cuba?
她可以去牙买加吸大麻
She can smoke weed in Jamaica.
宝贝  那可是牙买加
Come on, honey. It's Jamaica.
她说得没错  妈  这是有区别的
She's right, Mom. It's something different.
你能想象埃迪的样子吗
Can you imagine Eddie?
他肯定回不来了
He'd never make it back.
他会忘记自己的名字  可怜虫
He'd forget his name, that poor guy.
这笑话不错
That was a good joke.
不  妈  我很严肃
No, Mom, I'm serious.
我得接一下电话  受不了牙买加了
I gotta take this because Jamaican me crazy.
-不好笑  亲爱的  -根本不好笑
- That's not funny, baby. - That's not funny.
你觉得他们会去干什么
What do you think they're gonna be doing?
做爱呗
She's gonna bang.
我走了  我要回去了
You guys, I should go. I should get back.
-肯定要做爱  -没错
- They're going to. - Yes.
别碰我  我要吃蛋糕
Don't touch me. I'm gonna get cake.
这蛋糕真好吃
That shit was good.
戴尔
Delly?
不  不
No, no, no!
阿道夫  阿道夫
Adolfo! Adolfo!
-怎么回事  -快叫人来
- What happened? What happened? - Call someone! Call someone!
打电话
Call someone!
打电话啊  米格尔
Call somebody. Miguel, call somebody.
不要啊  戴尔菲
No, Delfia.
戴尔菲  不
Delfi, no...
小子  如果你现在不面对现实
Hey, kid, if you don't face this now...
我记得我第一次杀人
I remember my first.
跟你差不多大
I was a minute younger than you.
我还记得指尖上火药的味道
I still remember the smell of the heat on my fingertips.
那味道...
That shit...
那味道不会消散
That shit wouldn't go away.
我记得...
I remember...
我记得吃我妈做的
I remember smelling it when I went to take a bite
火腿三明治时闻到过
of this ham sandwich my old girl made me.
我记得我对自己说...
And I remember thinking, saying to myself...
这是我杀人后第一次吃东西
This the first time I'm eating as a person who killed someone.
我记得洗澡时在想...
I remember taking a shower thinking...
在想同一件事
thinking the same thing.
这是我杀人后...
This the first shower...
第一次洗澡
since becoming a killer.
我记得骑车时
I remember riding a bike.
第一次打球时
First time playing ball.
第一次  第一次
First time, first time.
我完全变了样
All as this new person.
但好笑的是  我都不记得
And the funny thing is, the nigga that I killed,
我杀的那个人叫什么了
I don't even remember his name.
伊兹·莫拉莱斯
尼克
Nick.
我记得自己迫不得已打死了他
I remember I shot him 'cause I had to.
他不死我就得死
It was me or him.
但我扣动扳机后...
But after I squeezed that trigger...
就被改变了
I let that shit change me.
罪恶感像癌症一样钻进骨头里
Get inside my bones like some cancer
蔓延至全身
all up and through every part of who I was.
我被自己的罪孽重新定义了
I let my sin define me,
它将我磨成了
grind me down
我表面上装出来的那个人
to the man I thought I 'posed to be.
但你不用这样  儿子
But you ain't got to do that, son.
这座城市...
This town...
将由你自己造就
it's what you make it.
你要明白
You need to know that.
你可以选择
You got a choice.
我们都可以选择
We all got choice.
人生就在于选择
Life about choice.
我的选择
And the choices I make,
并不总是那么好看
they ain't always gonna be pretty.
事实上  有时很难看
Hell, matter of fact, sometimes they gonna be ugly.
有人会拿枪对着我们
There's gonna be people gunning for us.
我说的不是
And I ain't talkin' about them kids
跟你们在利特尔里弗打架的人
you throw down with in Little River
或是唐纳家的人
or even them Towners.
我说的这些人更可怕
Dawg, I'm talking a whole lot worse.
因为在这里...
'Cause here, where we at...
一举一动都伴随着代价
every move you make, it come with a price.
他会消灭他们...
So He will knock them down...
你得愿意付出代价...
And you got to be willing to pay that price...
继续前行...
and move on...
听到我的祝福...
Hear the sound of my prayers...
每一滴泪水都值得
and know that it's worth every tear.
我举起双手...
I raise my hands...
每一滴汗
Every ounce of sweat.
别将我带走...
Don't drag me away...
每一滴血
Every drop of blood.
因为这里不是美国  孩子
'Cause this ain't America, kid.
这里是迈阿密
This here is Miami.